If you open up the link to the XML visualizer, that we provided
Eğitmen notlarında bulunan XML Visualizer (Görüntüleyici)
you in the instructor notes, then this is what it would look like.
bağlantısını açtığınızda, işte böyle görünür.
We have a linear layout with a text view that says Guest List and
"Guest List" yazan bir Text View ve "Kunal" yazan bir Text View'in
another text view that says Kunal.
olduğu bir LinearLayout'umuz var.
The first task was to add more text views to create the guest list.
İlk görev, davetli listesini oluşturmak için daha fazla Text View eklemek.
So let's copy and paste this XML element.
Bu XML elementini kopyalayıp yapıştıralım.
Cool, let's add some other people besides Kunal.
Harika, Kunal dışında başka kişileri de ekleyelim.
Let's add Kagure and also Lyla.
Kagure'ı ekleyelim ve ve Lyla'yı da.
Awesome.
Müthiş.
So now Kagure and Lyla show up under Kunal's name.
Şimdi Kunal'ın ismi altında Kagure ve Lyla'da görünüyor.
We can also change any of the existing text use.
Mevcut TextView'i de değiştirebiliriz.
We change to the VIP list.
"VIP List" olarak değiştirelim.
The second task was to change the orientation attribute to be horizontal.
İkinci görev, yön özelliğini yatay olarak değiştirmekti.
This immediately changes all the text views to appear side by side
Bu değişiklik, hemen bütün metnin alt alta olması yerine,
instead of one on top of the other.
yan yana görünmesini sağladı.